<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Hidden Camera Detection System</string>
    <string name="magnetic_radiation_message">If the reading is high even without the existence of any cameras or devices, please shake your phone gently or initialize the sensor by pointing your phone up and rotate it in "8" pattern.</string>
    <string name="OK">OK</string>
    <string name="Important">Important</string>
    <string name="magnetic_radiation_instruction">Move the application near any suspicious objects. If the readings are similar to camera reading (90µF-140µF) there may be hidden camera(s).</string>

    <!--bathroom string-->
    <string name="activity_bathroom_title">The possibility of hidden camera be positioned in a bathroom is 12%</string>
    <string name="activity_bathroom">Check on the devices listed below (for manual scanning, look for lens-like parts over devices listed below)\n\n1. Water heater: turn off the heater before checking and then precisely check the shower head as well as the surrounding.\n\n2. Mirror: touch the mirror and check if there is any gap between your fingers and the mirror glass. The mirror is safe to use if there is a gap in between your fingers and the mirror glass. On the contrary, a camera could be hidden right behind the mirror glass if there appears no gap between your fingers and the mirror glass.\n\n3. Ceiling or smoke detector: Use a sticker or tape to cover the viewable part of the detector in the bathroom if you are feeling unsafe. This is a precaution step to protect yourself and your privacy from being the victim of a hidden camera case.\n\n4. Lamps or bulbs: Use curtains to cover the lamps and bulbs in the bathroom if you are feeling under surveillance.\n\nDo lodge a complaint to the authorities if you are feeling unsafe or find anything suspicious in the bathroom.\n\nTake your personal privacy to the extreme as personal privacy is not for sale and it should not be compromised out of fear or greed.</string>

    <!--fitting room-->
    <string name="activity_fitting_room_title">The possibility of hidden camera be positioned in a fitting room is 12%</string>
    <string name="activity_fitting_room">Check on the devices listed below (for manual scanning, look for lens-like parts over devices listed below)\n\n1. Mirror: touch the mirror and check if there is any gap between your fingers and the mirror glass. The mirror is safe to use if there is a gap in between your fingers and the mirror glass. On the contrary, a camera could be hidden right behind the mirror glass if there appears no gap between your fingers and the mirror glass.\n\n2. Hangers: Precisely check the lens-like aperture on the hangers, especially screw-like objects as it could be an ideal position to insert a hidden camera. Put clothes over the hangers to cover all the screws.\n\n3. Ceiling or smoke detector: Use clothes to cover the viewable part of the detector in the fitting room if you are feeling unsafe. This is a precaution step to protect yourself and your privacy from being the victim of a hidden camera case.\n\nDo lodge a complaint to the shop workers, shop owners or authorities if you are feeling unsafe or find anything suspicious in the fitting room.\n\nTake your personal privacy to the extreme as personal privacy is not for sale and it should not be compromised out of fear or greed.</string>


    <!--room-->
    <string name="activity_room_title">The possibility of hidden camera be positioned in a hotel room is 15%</string>
    <string name="activity_room">Check on the devices listed below (for manual scanning, look for lens-like parts over devices listed below)\n\n1. Ceiling or smoke detector: Use a sticker or tape to cover the viewable part of the detector in the hotel room if you are feeling unsafe. This is a precaution step to protect yourself and your privacy from being the victim of a hidden camera case.\n\n2. Air conditioner: Precisely check the air conditioner vent before switching it on. Cover the air conditioner vent with a towel or clothes if you find it suspicious. You could also use the fans provided in the room and keep the air conditioner switched off if you are feeling under surveillance.\n\n3. Television: Keep the main power supply switched off if you are not using the television. You could also place your belongings in front of the lens-like part of the television to keep it covered.\n\n4. Night lamp: Keep it switched off if it is not in use or change its direction to face the wall.\n\n5. Flower pot: Change its position to the least viewable area if there are any flower pots placed in your hotel room.\n\n6. Coffee maker: Unplug it and put it inside a cupboard or cover it with a towel if you find it suspicious.\n\nDo lodge a complaint to the hotel workers, hotel owners or authorities if you are feeling unsafe or find anything suspicious in the hotel room.\n\nTake your personal privacy to the extreme as personal privacy is not for sale and it should not be compromised out of fear or greed.</string>

    <!--outdoor-->
    <string name="activity_outdoor_title">You might be monitored under a CCTV</string>
    <string name="activity_outdoor">Keep yourself well-behaved whenever you are in the outdoors. You might not be able to hide your identity in outdoor places so you should be cautious when you are in unfamiliar places or outdoors. It is important to pay attention to the surroundings all the time to protect yourself from being monitored illegally.\n\nDo lodge a complaint to the patrol or authorities if you are feeling unsafe or find anything suspicious when you are in the outdoors.\n\nTake your personal privacy to the extreme as personal privacy is not for sale and it should not be compromised out of fear or greed.</string>

</resources>